<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">
	<!-- <NameField>Self-Insert</NameField> -->
	<NameField>Leuc</NameField>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>START</Name>
		<EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Oh! Thank goodness you are here! I have lost my cat. I can't find him anywhere! Can you please help me?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<DialogueOptionsList>
		
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>I am already searching for him!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>HUB_1</DialogueTarget>
				<RequiredLogCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_LOOKING_FOR_CAT</RequiredLogCondition>
			</DialogueOption>
		
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Of course, I will help you find your cat!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>QUEST_GET</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>No, I do not care about your cat.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>DO_NOT_CARE</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Tell me about the mod.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ABOUT_MOD</DialogueTarget>
				<RequiredLogCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_YOU_WIN</RequiredLogCondition>
			</DialogueOption>
			
		</DialogueOptionsList>
		
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>TALK_AGAIN</Name>
		<EntryCondition>TALKED_ONCE</EntryCondition>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hello again! Have you found my cat yet?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<DialogueTarget>HUB_1</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>DO_NOT_CARE</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>What? Then why did you install this mod...?</Page>
			<Page>Well, fine. I'm sure the other Jam 5 entries ought to be better than this one, anyway. I'll be here if you change your mind.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>QUEST_GET</Name>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Excellent! Then it is time to start investigating the Mystery of "I Cannot Find My Cat"!</Page> <!-- KYLE REFERENVEASDFJKL -->
		</Dialogue>
		
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>LEESPORK_JAM5_LOOKING_FOR_CAT</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
		
		<DialogueTarget>HUB_1</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>HUB_1</Name>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>...</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<SetCondition>TALKED_ONCE</SetCondition>
		
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>So, where might your cat actually be?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>TRUE_CAT_LOCATION_HINT</DialogueTarget>
				<RequiredLogCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_CAT_VASE_COORDS</RequiredLogCondition>
			</DialogueOption>
		
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>I found a recording you left on the vessel in Dim Thorn. Your "cat" has been a cactus this entire time?!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ITS_A_CACTUS</DialogueTarget>
				<RequiredLogCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_VESSEL_RECORDER_RUMOUR</RequiredLogCondition>
			</DialogueOption>
		
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Your cat is not on the North tree, you left a recording there saying something about a Dim Thorn?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>CAT_NOT_ON_TREE</DialogueTarget>
				<RequiredLogCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_TREE_RECORDER</RequiredLogCondition>
			</DialogueOption>
		
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>I could not find your cat swimming in Dwarf's Shallow.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>CAT_NOT_SWIMMING</DialogueTarget>
				<RequiredLogCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_CACTUS_TELEPORTER_SPOTTED</RequiredLogCondition>
			</DialogueOption>

			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Where did you last see your cat?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>LAST_SEE_CAT</DialogueTarget>
				<CancelledCondition>REMEMBERS_CAT_NOT_ON_TREE</CancelledCondition>
			</DialogueOption>

			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Where did you last see your cat?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>LAST_SEE_CAT_NOT_TREE</DialogueTarget>
				<RequiredCondition>REMEMBERS_CAT_NOT_ON_TREE</RequiredCondition>
			</DialogueOption>
		
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Tell me about the mod.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ABOUT_MOD</DialogueTarget>
				<RequiredLogCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_YOU_WIN</RequiredLogCondition>
			</DialogueOption>
			
		</DialogueOptionsList>
		
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>LAST_SEE_CAT</Name>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>I believe I last saw him climbing the tree on the North Pole of this planet. Just follow the red beacon on your mini-map, I'm sure you'll find the tree!</Page>
			<Page>That'd be a good place for you to start searching for him. You know how cats are, always climbing trees. I don't know why I haven't looked there myself!</Page>
			<!-- Only giving one location for the player to explore is lame -->
			<Page>Or maybe I last saw him swimming in Dwarf's Shallow? You know, that green water planet. You might need a spaceship to go there, though.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>LEESPORK_JAM5_CAT_LAST_SEEN</FactID>
			<FactID>LEESPORK_JAM5_SWIMMING</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
		
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>CAT_NOT_ON_TREE</Name>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Oh! Of course! How embarrassing, I must have mixed up Dim Thorn and the tree... They are both plants, after all...</Page>
			<Page>Gosh I hope my cat is alright, Dim Thorn is not a very safe place at all! I can't enter it anyway, it is is too small, and thorny. And Dim.</Page>
			<Page>But, can you please give it a shot? It looks like a small seed, and it is the furthest object orbiting my sun.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<SetCondition>REMEMBERS_CAT_NOT_ON_TREE</SetCondition>
		
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>LAST_SEE_CAT_NOT_TREE</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>It must have been Dim Thorn! Thank you for jogging my memory.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ITS_A_CACTUS</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Ohh! That's right! Dim Thorn wasn't the last place I saw my cat, it was the FIRST!</Page>
			<Page>And yeah, my cat is a catcus! That is what "cat" is short for! What did you think it was?</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>It is pronounced "cactus." And a cat is an animal!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ITS_A_CACTUS_2A</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>...Fine, whatever. I'll find you "catcus" for you.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ITS_A_CACTUS_2B</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ITS_A_CACTUS_2A</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>It is? Oh gosh, how embarrassing. I see how you were confused. Sorry about that!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>ITS_A_CACTUS_3</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ITS_A_CACTUS_2B</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Excellent!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>ITS_A_CACTUS_3</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ITS_A_CACTUS_3</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>So yeah, my catcus. Cactus? My beloved cat. I would be forever grateful if you returned it to me! It goes in this thin little vase next to me.</Page>
			<Page>Oh, that reminds me, you'll probably need some help getting it into my vase!</Page>
			<Page>I can give you the exact co-ordinates to it, in the cactus professional standard. I am a well practised cactus professional, after years of cactus ownership - as good as any trained one in fact!</Page>
			<Page>Here. Now, if you find any cactus transporting devices, you can bring my cat right to me!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>LEESPORK_JAM5_CAT_VASE_COORDS</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>So, where might your cat actually be?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>TRUE_CAT_LOCATION_HINT</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Thanks, that is all I need!</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>GOODBYE_GL</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>TRUE_CAT_LOCATION_HINT</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hmm... So my cat is not on Log Fireplace, not swimming in Dwarf's Shallow, not inside Dim Thorn...</Page>
			<Page>So where could he be?! He could be anywhere! He could be right under our noses!</Page>
			<Page>Have you tried looking under your bed? Underneath the <![CDATA[<color=orange>platform</color>]]>?</Page>
			<Page>Don't forget, you are looking for a relatively small cactus that has a little flower on top.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>GOODBYE_GL</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Good luck!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>WIN_START</Name>
		<EntryCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_CACTUS_RETURNED</EntryCondition>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>My cat has been returned to me! Thank you so much!</Page>
			<Page>So my cat was on the Central Station the whole time? You know come to think of it, why did I not consider that my cat could have used this giant warp pad that is directly in front of me?</Page>
			<Page>But the important thing is, now we are together again, and we can now live our last moments together happily in peace.</Page>
			<Page>One could say the time we have remaining together until the sun explodes is <![CDATA[<color=orange>miniature</color>]]>, but the love we feel for each other is anything but!</Page>
			<Page>(Congratulations on beating the mod!)</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<RevealFacts>
			<FactID>LEESPORK_JAM5_YOU_WIN</FactID>
			<FactID>LEESPORK_JAM5_CACTUS_IDENTITY</FactID>
			<FactID>LEESPORK_JAM5_CACTUS_GONE_HOME</FactID>
		</RevealFacts>
		
		<SetCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_DIE_HAPPY</SetCondition>
		
	</DialogueNode>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>POST_WIN</Name>
		<EntryCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_DIE_HAPPY</EntryCondition>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Thank you again! I will never forget you for as long as I live!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Tell me about the mod</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ABOUT_MOD</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Goodbye Leuc</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>GOODBYE_FINAL</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>CAT_NOT_SWIMMING</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hmmm... I must have been mistaken...</Page>
			<Page>That makes a lot of sense actually, now that I think about it. My cat doesn't like swimming! He hates being over watered! What was I thinking?!</Page>
			<Page>He must be at that other place I told you about.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>OTHER_CREDITS</Name>
		
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Anyway, no mod is made in a vacuum, so here are the extended credits!</Page>
			
			<Page>Special thanks to the developer(s) of the xen.NewHorizonsExamples mod, which I used for reference material for developing this mod.</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to the developer(s) of the xen.PlayAsGabbro mod, which I also used for reference.</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to the developer(s) of the xen-42.ModJam5 mod, which I also used for reference.</Page>
			<Page>Wait, did I just thank Xen three times? Anyway...</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to the developer(s) of the Trifid.TrifidJam3 mod, which I also used as reference.</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to the developer(s) of the LeeSpork.ModJam5 m- No wait, that's me.</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to all the contributors of New Horizons and its online documentation, for making this mod possible despite me not bothering to learn how to code or create assets for Outer Wilds.</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to the developers of Outer Wilds, for obvious reasons.</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to the judges of the 5th Outer Wilds Mod Jam, who are presumably going to be judging this despite the fact that is clearly not going to win...</Page>
			<Page>And are therefore about to give me $0 in prize money, which means I win because the theme was miniature and you can't get much smaller than nothing!</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to Notepad++, even though I really should have been using something that actually checks the schemas to alert me if my code is invalid...</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to Paint.NET, and BoltBait's Black and White+ v6.0 plugin.</Page>
			<Page>Special thanks to the Firefox web browser, in which I currently have seven thousand five hundred and seventy-four tabs open across twenty-three windows.</Page>
			<Page>And a very special thanks to the members of the Outer Wilds Modding Discord server!</Page>
			<Page>Also, more than a special thanks to the organisers and judges of the fifth Outer Wilds mod jam! (Yes I just thanked Xen again.)</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<SetCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_SPECIAL_THANKED</SetCondition>
		
		<DialogueTarget>JAM_EXTENTION</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>WRONG_CACTUS</Name>
		<EntryCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_WRONG_CACTUS_IN_VASE</EntryCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>This is <![CDATA[<color=orange><size=50>NOT</size></color>]]> MY CAT!</Page>
			<Page>Mine is <![CDATA[<color=orange><size=25>miniature</size></color>]]>, not <![CDATA[<color=lightblue><size=50>oversized</size></color>]]>!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<SetCondition>LEESPORK_JAM5_LEUC_KILLS_YOU</SetCondition>
		<DialogueTarget>BIG_NO</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>BIG_NO</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page><![CDATA[<i>NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</i>]]></Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>GOODBYE_FINAL</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Farewell!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ABOUT_MOD</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>I will now talk on behalf of the mod's creator, LeeSpork. Thank you for playing my mod!</Page>
			<Page>If you enjoyed it, please let me know! Or even if you didn't, I would love to hear your thoughts on it!</Page>
			<Page>This was my first Outer Wilds mod! Just a simple New Horizons plugin to get my foot in the door. I sadly didn't have enough willpower to get started with 3D modelling and custom programming in time for the mod jam.</Page>
			<Page>Speaking of, I'm so glad I was able to compete in a mod jam! Even if there was never any chance of me actually winning. The miniature star systems theme of this mod jam was also a great one for a first-time modder, keeping the scope nice and contained.</Page>
			<Page>I actually didn't start making this mod until almost a week in, simply because I had no idea what I wanted the mod to be about.</Page>
			<Page>Eventually, I settled on what you just played, even though it doesn't follow the "miniature" theme super well.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>This dialogue is kind of long, can I leave?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>TRAP</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Please go on, I wish to hear about everything in excruciating detail.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>ABOUT_MOD_CONT</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>TRAP</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Ha! You have fallen victim to one of the classic blunders. This dialogue is not ending any time soon...</Page>
			<Page>And now that you have started this dialogue, you cannot leave!</Page>
			<Page><![CDATA[And in addition, the theme of this jam was <color=orange>miniature</color>, and <i>I therefore made the supernova happen was sooner than normal!</i>]]></Page>
			<Page>Now you will be doomed to listen to me <![CDATA[<i>until the sun explodes!</i>]]></Page>
			<Page>So, where was I...</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>ABOUT_MOD_CONT</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>ABOUT_MOD_CONT</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>This whole plot was actually based on a quote from the 2019 text-based adventure game "Kyle is Famous", which is on Steam.</Page>
			<Page>There is a part in the Complete Edition where the narrator says "It was time to investigate the mystery of... I cannot find my cat."</Page>
			<Page>I thought this quote was funny, hence the entire story of this mod.</Page>
			<Page>Leuc was originally named "Self-Insert", which is why they use the "self" NPC model. However, I realised that the plot only works if the cat owner is dysfunctional in a way that I am not, so I changed them to be a fictional character to avoid any implications.</Page>
			<Page>As for the planets, you may have noticed that they are parodies of the planets from the base game. When I was brainstorming mini solar system ideas for this mod jam, it was the most obvious option to just remake the Outer Wilds, but smaller.</Page>
			<Page>Of course, you may have noticed several key locations are missing, most notable Brittle Hollow and the Hourglass Twins.</Page>
			<Page>I considered parodying the Hourglass Twins by having a warp core orbiting the sun, since it kind of looks like an hourglass, and certainly fits the "miniature" bill!</Page>
			<Page>Though I decided against it in the end, since I didn't want to mislead players who might assume it would be a key item.</Page>
			<Page>For the Brittle Hollow analog, I was going to add a black hole orbiting between Log Fireplace and Dwarf's Shallow. Leuc would call the player's attention to it, saying something about how there used to be a planet there, but now it's just a hole.</Page>
			<Page>Falling into the black hole would of course then take you to the White Hole Train Station, above the plane of the solar system.</Page>
			<Page>But I couldn't figure out how to fit it into the story, and of course I would be very limited on time to somehow model a train station anyway, so it didn't make it into the final mod.</Page>
			<Page>Speaking of not making it into the final mod, I couldn't figure out how to work with the Probe Control Module asset. The only other stand-alone Nomai building asset with collision that I could find was the tower on the quantum moon, however, the top and bottom of that model is not closed. In the end, the Nomai escape pod was way easier to work with, so that is what I went with for the structure in the core of Dwarf's Shallow.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>OTHER_CREDITS</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>MOD_PROBLEMS_RANT</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>So, what problems did I encounter while making this mod?</Page>
			
			<Page>One really silly issue I discovered was that the size of the supernova blast is inversely proportional to the supernova speed, even ignoring the configured supernova size value.</Page>
			<Page>I tried setting the speed really low so that you could escape it, but this resulted in it eating the entire rest of Jam 5!</Page>
			
			<Page>One issue I had was due to how I used the vessel geometry copied directly from the base game's Dark Bramble. The collision of the entire bramble dimension it is inside was baked into its collisions, and it does not line up with bramble dimensions created with New Horizons!</Page>
			<Page>I solved this by simply making the bramble dimension way smaller, which is why the vessel is proportionally closer to the entrance than it is in the base game.</Page>
			<Page>Another issue I had in the vessel was the Hearthian recorder's dialogue not working. Turns out, it doesn't work if the dialogue is placed with its centre point exactly in the ground!</Page>
			
			<Page>Another silly thing was that this planet, Log Fireplace, is so small that when I first added the geyser to it, the very bottom of it went right through the planet and appeared upside-down inside the warp pad!</Page>
			<Page>It was strong enough that it could even prevent the player from entering the warp pad's black hole! Wanted to return to Central Station and got the cycle on the geyser wrong? Too bad lol!</Page>
			<Page>Luckily, fixing this was as simple as increasing the offset of the geyser.</Page>
			
			<Page>Another thing that I discovered the hard way was that getting hit by the supernova while sleeping can cause you to never wake up.</Page>
			<Page>Well, I suppose you already know that, because I wrote a note next to the campfire to warn you of it...</Page>
			<Page>I slept right through the end of the loop! It goes past 22 minutes, and then it just keeps going! I had to Alt+F4 the game to escape!</Page>
			<Page>I'm not actually sure if that still happens. Maybe it had to do with the supernova size bug I mentioned before? But like, better safe than sorry.</Page>
			
			<Page>I have some complaints about New Horizons.</Page>
			
			<Page>For a stellar remnant, it turns out you have to explicitly remove the ship log for it, else the ship log computer bugs out and softlocks the game if the player tries to use it. I guess because it's the same planet ID as the star?</Page>
			<Page>It is not documented that you have to do this. And why can't it just do that automatically?</Page>
			
			<Page>On detail props, I found no way of removing specific components. You either remove all components, or none of them.</Page>
			<Page>I had to remove the components of this very NPC, in case you are wondering, because otherwise there would be a "YOU ARE HERE" marker the map here.</Page>
			
			<Page>Another thing, the docs do not specify that the value of "curve" is influenced by the size value. I assumed it would be setting the size to the value, but actually, it is a multiplier of its size.</Page>
			<Page>But wait, that's not true either! It is also, at least in the case of sand, doubled?! And this isn't documented at all, you just have to figure it out..</Page>
			
			<Page>Also you cannot set more than one condition at once in a dialogue option, which was a little inconvenient.</Page>
			
			<Page><![CDATA[My biggest concern, the Name field of celestial objects is used as the <i>unique ID</i> for that planet. But it is also used for the <i>display name</i> of that planet, like on the map and on the ship log's map mode! Why?!]]></Page>
			<Page>It is very lucky that my planets have no name conflicts with other Jam 5 mods, considering I did the very creative thing of just doing a miniature parody of the original Outer Wilds system!</Page>
			<Page>By the way, the Outer Wilds system is already very very <![CDATA[<i>very</i>]]> miniature compared to real ones, so that makes my entry miniature squared? I win! Or well I guess not since everyone's entry is the same 2500 meters radius... whatever.</Page>
			
			<Page>So I might have to be submitting some issues to the New Horizons GitHub after this...</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<DialogueTarget>SO_UHH</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>SO_UHH</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>So uhh... You're still here?</Page>
			<Page>Haven't been killed by the supernova yet?</Page>
			<Page>Or perhaps you skipped through the dialogue to get to this point?</Page>
			<Page>If you actually read all of this, you are super.</Page>
			<Page>I don't have anything else for you though...</Page>
			<Page>Uhh....</Page>
			<Page>I love fish and chips.</Page>
			<Page>I hate Stardew Valley.</Page>
			<Page>...</Page>
			<Page>.....................................</Page>
			<Page>Okay fine, you can go.</Page>
			<Page>I can't believe you escaped my super-long dialogue under a short-lived star trap!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>JAM_EXTENTION</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>With that done... Did you know that this mod jam had a two-day extension?</Page>
			<Page>Even though I planned around not having an extension and made sure my mod was ready by the original deadline, I'm glad there was one!</Page>
			<Page>One person on Discord was complaining about how barren a few of the platforms in the Central Station were, so I made use of the extension to add potted trees to mine.</Page>
			<Page>Of course I already had those two benches - one with a spork representing me, and an empty one just for you, dear player! But on their own, they still didn't really help you tell apart my platform at a glance, being such small details.</Page>
			<Page>I also used the extension to add this whole line of dialogue! If there wasn't an extension, Leuc would have nothing more to say after you got congratulated for completing the mod.</Page>
			<Page>Yeah that's right, if the other modders were more diligent and had finished their jam entries on time, you wouldn't have to be listening through any of this rambling!</Page>
			<Page>No offense meant to them though, the extension was well-deserved! Besides, this whole dialogue trap thing was also something that I intended to add from the start but didn't have time to prioritise until the extension was announced.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		
		<DialogueTarget>MOD_PROBLEMS_RANT</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>


</DialogueTree> <!-- This is the end of the file -->
